<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Liquori | Developer</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 14:48:23 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 14:48:23 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How This Blog Was Made</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 05:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//blog/meta/html/jekyll/2015/01/29/how-this-blog-was-made.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//blog/meta/html/jekyll/2015/01/29/how-this-blog-was-made.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>meta</category>
        
        <category>html</category>
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To My Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, and welcome to my blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this post, I will note the motivation for creating this blog, and a little about me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have recently embarked on a journey to become a professional software developer. My technical expertise is primarily statistics and finance (data science), and I am very excited to expand into working with the visual and user experience (UX) aspects of design. I love to make things that are streamlined and elegant to the senses, while of course also providing great, error-free and efficient functionality under the hood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Blog:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not infrequently, we can run into a concept that we are just unable to really grasp, until we arrive to a singular explanation that seems to have been made especially for our brains, which hoists us over the mental wall and allows us to keep moving. One aim of this blog is to return a few of the infinite favors the web has bestowed upon me over the years, by providing clear explanations that might allow others to achieve a similar breakthrough moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondarily, writing this blog will no doubt help me, as writing and teaching a concept to others is a great way to explore and cement new concepts in your mind, even if that someone else is an imaginary reader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&quot;/blog/meta/html/jekyll/2015/01/29/how-this-blog-was-made.html&quot;&gt;next post&lt;/a&gt;, I will go over the steps I followed to create this site.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 05:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//blog/meta/2015/01/28/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mliq.github.io/Jekyll//blog/meta/2015/01/28/welcome-to-my-blog.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>meta</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
